Guide to the Charles Owen Rice Papers, 1894-2005 AIS.1976.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Subject Files, 1894-2005; I.
  - Prisoner Correspondence [RESTRICTED]
    - 1996, [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - 1997, [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - 1998, [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - 1999, [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - 2000-2001, [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Albert, Eugene, undated; [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Allegheny County Jail, 1981-1985; [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Allen, George L., 1970-1973; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Allen, James, 1972-1974; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Amaker, James, 1973; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Austin, Robert, 1972; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Baker, Frank S., 1963; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Baskin, Burrell, 1970-1974; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Baskin, Joe, 1973; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Bayles, Earl C., 1959; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Bell, Hubert, 1973; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Black, Debbie, 1972-1974; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Blackwell, Edward D., 1974; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Bomar, John, 1969; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Boyd, Donald J., 1973; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Boyd, James R., 1973; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Bricker, Robert L., 1970; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Bright, James, 1975; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Brock, Melvin, 1972-1974; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Brockelbank, Larry, 1971; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Brooks, Eugene, 1959; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Brown, Earl, 1972; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Butler, John, 1975-1976; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Charles, Moses, 1968; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Chisholm, Lawrence, 1975-1976; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Claybrook, Byron, 1968-1969; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Codispoti, Dominick, 1975-1976; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Collington, LeRoy A., 1975; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Corcoran, Russell G., 1971; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Cotton, Alonzo, 1974; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Cotton, Jeremiah, 1969-1970; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Cox, Myron F., 1970; [RESTRICTED] (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Critten, Edward M., 1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Davenport, Ken and Calvin Johnson, 1992-2000; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Davenport, Ken and Calvin Johnson, 1992-2000; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - David, George T., 1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Davis, Vincent, 1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Dennison, Homer, 1970-1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Dorsey, Howard, 1965; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Dunscomb, Kenneth, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Earley, Alfred, 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Eason, Corp. Charles III, 1971-1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Eckhart, Claude, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Ellis, James, 1965; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Englert, John, 1964; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Fields, Harold, 1975-1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Fitzgerald, Buddy M., 1969; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Flack, Robert J., 1974-1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Fletcher, James M., 1970-1972; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Foschia, Rudy, 1960-1963; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Foster, Bernard, 1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Frederick, Andrew G.W., 1967; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Futch, Clifford, 1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Gamble, Blaine X., 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Gasperic, George, 1970; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Gaston, Henry, 1972-1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Giles, Raymond, 1970; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Gordon, Garfield, Jr., 1974-1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Gregg, Richard, 1970; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Haden, William, 1988-1995; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Hamilton, Randy, 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Hamlin, Clarence, 1969; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Hart, John L., 1972; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Hines, William, 1986-1997; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Hines, William, 1998-2002; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Hines, William, Case, 1988; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Hines, William, Commutation, 1987-1988; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Hoover, Elder, 1967; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Hopkins, Richard, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Howard, Kenneth, 1972; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Howell, William, 1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Jefferson, Tony, 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Johnson, Alvin X., 1974-1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Johnson, Carlton, 1969; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Johnson, Carlton, 1969-1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Johnson, Gerald, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Johnston, Don J., 1961; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Jones, Charles W., 1970-1972; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Jones, Robert, 1970; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Kemp, Lewis, 1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Kennedy, Frank, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Kershaw, Harry, 1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Kosalko, George, 1967-1969; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Koveleskie, Frank, 1972; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Lawson, Aldon, 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Lockhart, Sylvester, Jr., 1970-1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Lyons, Paul T., 1971-1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Malarkey, Harold, 1964; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Mayberry, Richard O.J., 1975-1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Mayberry, Richard O.J., 1975-2002; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Mayberry, Richard O.J., 1975-2002; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - Mayberry, Richard O.J., 1975-2002; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - Mayberry, Richard O.J., 1975-2002; (RESTRICTED) (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - Mayo, Gerald, 1988-2001; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Mazzoccoli, Howard, 1974-1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - McGrogan, Robert E., 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - McGuire, Charles, 1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Miller, William, 1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Moeller, Charlotte J., 1959-1963; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Montgomery, Donald H., 1973-1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Moran, David A., 1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Morris, William, 1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Nusser, Norman C., 1989-1992; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nusser, Norman C., 1989-1992; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Nusser, Norman C., 1989-1992; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Olds, Ricky, 1983; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Oliver, Lonzy, 1969-1970; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Oliverio, John J., 1963; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Ostine, Joyce, 1966; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Owens, Kenneth W., 1970; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Pacek, Jerry, 1961; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Parker, Lee D., 1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Patterson, Leon, 1980; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Patterson, Leon, 1980; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Payne, Evans, 1971-1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Perkins, Ronald, undated; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Peters, Willie, 1967-1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Petrisko, J. George, 1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Phillips, Earl D., 1962; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Plair, Wade, 1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Powell, Leslie, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Pratt, Louis, undated; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Rakus, Frank, 1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Riley, Jacob, 1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Ringer, Solomon, 1967-1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Russell, Barney, 1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Sanders, William H., 1972; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Sauveur, Frank H., 1958; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Schneck, Geoffrey B., 1961-1962; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Sero, Joseph, 1992; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Sherrell, Timothy, 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Sivlar, Fred, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Smith, James C., 1972-1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Smith, Landrew, 1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Rayford, 1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Sprangle, Cornelius J., 1970; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Stark, Robert M., 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Steele, Gregory, 1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Stevenson, Leonard J., 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Stewart, James L., 1956; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Thomas, Paul, 1972; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Tyler, Aaron, 1976; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Tyus, James, 1968; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Wall, James E., 1969-1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Webster, Darryl, 1972-1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Williams, Clarence B., 1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Wilson, George, 1966-1973; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Wood, William W., 1964; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Zumda, Robert, 1971; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Father Rice's Defense Fund, 1973-1974; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Letters Regarding, 1968-1975; (RESTRICTED) (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Prisoners, Newsletter, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Prisoners, Rights Newsletter, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Prisoners, United Inmate Advocacy Council, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Prisons, Pennsylvania Board of Pardons Schedule of Sessions, 1972, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Prisons, Pennsylvania Citizens for Corrections, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Prisons, Probation and Parole, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Prisons, Profit, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Prisons, Reform, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Prisons, Reform, Meeting with Governor Shapp, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Problem Cases, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Pro Deo, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Project Equality, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Public Interest Research Group, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Quill, Michael, 1955-1970 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Quill, Mike, "The Communists and City Hall", 1971 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Quotations, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - R Productions, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Race Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Racial Integration, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Racial Integration, Bussing, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Racial Justice, Neuman Lectures, 1960-1969 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Racial Segregation, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Railroads, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Railway Clerks, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Randolph, A. Philip, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Ready Youth Fund, 1968-1975 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Religion Labor Conference, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Religious Agency for Human Renewal, Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Religious Agency for Human Renewal, Financial Statements, 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Religious Agency for Human Renewal, General Information, 1965-1970 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Religious Agency for Human Renewal, Minutes, 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Religious Agency for Human Renewal, News Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Religious Agency for Human Renewal, Resumes, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Rent Administration, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Rent Control, 1940-1945 (Box 17, Folder 34, Folder 35)
  - Requests for Favors from Unions, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Requests for Pamphlets, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Requests for Radio Broadcasts, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Research Institute of America, 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Retail Clerks, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Retail Food Store Employees, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Retirement, Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Retirement, News Clippings, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Retarded Children, Washington, Pennsylvania, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Rice, Joseph, Unions, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Rice, Peter, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Rice, Reverend, Articles About, 1945-1949 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Rice, Reverend, Miscellaneous Clippings, 1937-1969 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Right to Work Literature, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Riots, Article on, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Riot Fact Finding Reports, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rockwell Manufacturing Company, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rubber Workers, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Russell, Reverend W. Joyce, 1944-1947 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Russia and Other Trips, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - St. Agnes Parish, Pittsburgh, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - St. Anne Church, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - St. Basil Parish, Pittsburgh, PA, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - St. Benedict the Moor, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - St. Francis College, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - St. Francis College, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - St. Joseph Church, Natrona, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1940-1945 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1935-1947 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, 1987-1997 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, Accounts and Reports, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, Fundraising, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, Paid Bills, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, Reports, 1944-1948 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - St. Joseph House of Hospitality, Shipping Reports, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - St. Patrick's Day Luncheon, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - St. Patrick's Day Program, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Sane Nuclear Policy, Pittsburgh Committee, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - SAV-CAP, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Scabs, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Schatz, Ronald W., "American Labor and the Catholic Church", 1983 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - School Bus Bill, Parochial, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Sermons, Article on, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Seven-Eleven News, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Sherman Service Company, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Shoeworkers, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Shrine of St. Joseph, St. Louis, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Sign, Pictorial and Display Union, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Social Action Leaders, Ainsely, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Social Concern of the Church, 1980-1991 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Soft Drink Workers, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - South Africa, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Spanish Civil War, 1936-1938 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Spain, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    U.S. Committee for the Carabanchel 10
  - Speaking Engagements, 1938-1946 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Special Events, 1938-1942 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Speeches, 1937-1945 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Stackpole Carbon Company, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Standard Floor Company, Local 249, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America, Local 255, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Steel Workers, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Steel Workers, Election, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, Beaver Valley, 1938-1940 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, Charleroi, 1938-1940 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, Homestead, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, Kiski Valley, 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, Lawrenceville, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, McKees Rocks, 1938-1940 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Steel Workers, Organization Committee, South Side, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Steiner Manufacturing Company, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Steiner Manufacturing Company, Carrie Miller, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Steiner Manufacturing Company, Henrietta Murray, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Steiner Manufacturing Company, TWOA-CIO, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Sweeney, Vincent, United Steelworkers Association, Editor, Steelworker, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Sweet Clean Laundry, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Sweet Clean Laundry, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Sweet Clean Laundry, Arbitration, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Sweet Clean Laundry, Local 141, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Teachers, Right to Strike, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Teachers Union, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Team Ministry, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Telegraphers Union, 1937-1952 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Telegraph Workers, 1947-1950 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Telephone Workers, 1947-1950 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Testimonial Banquets, 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Textile Workers, 1942-1952 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Tighe, Bill, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Tighe, John M., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Transport Workers, 1937-1948 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Transport Workers Union, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Tri-State Conference on the Impact of Steel, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Trips, 1947-1957 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Trips, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - TV Projects, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Tyndale, Reverend John, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Uhuru poets, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Unemployed Protective Alliance, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Union Electric Steel Corporation, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Union Electric Steel Corporation, 1944-1946 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Unions, Miscellaneous, 1938-1948 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Unions, Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - United Auto Workers, 1939-1948 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - United Auto Workers, 1939-1948 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - United Auto Workers, 1939-1948 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - The United Automobile Workers, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Communism, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Progress, 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - United Electrical Workers, 1947-1950 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - United Electrical Workers, 1947-1950 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - United Electrical Workers, 1947-1950 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - United Electrical Workers, Canadian News, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - United Electrical Workers, Correspondence, A-C, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - United Electrical Workers, Correspondence, D-F, 1944-1950 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - United Electrical Workers, Correspondence, G-H, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - United Electrical Workers, Correspondence, I-Q, 1947-1950 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - United Electrical Workers, Correspondence, R-Z, 1943-1949 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - United Electrical Workers, Miscellaneous Clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - United Electrical Workers, Miscellaneous Clippings, 1946-1954 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - United Electrical Workers, News, 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - United Electrical Workers, Stewards Bulletin, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - United Electrical Workers, Union Generator, 1941-1950 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - United Electrical Workers, Union News, 1941-1948 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - United Electrical Workers, Voice of UE, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - United Electrical Workers, Voice of the U.E., 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 515)
  - United Food and Tobacco Workers Union, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - United Furniture Workers, 1947-1951 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers Union of America, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - United Mine Workers, 1942-1974 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - United Mine Workers of America, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, Committee for Industrial Organization, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America Membership Lists, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, Membership Lists, A-L, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, Membership Lists, M-Z, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - United Packing House Workers of America, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - United Public Workers of America, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - United Salary Workers, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - United States Catholic Historical Society, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - United States Committee for the Carabanchel 10, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - United States Department of Labor, Conciliation Service, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - United States Steel Corporation, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - United States Steel Corporation, Blacks, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - United Steel Workers of America, 1957-1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - United Steel Workers of America, Fiftieth Anniversary, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - United Steel Workers of America, History, 1936-1946 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - United Steel Workers of America, Reverend Rice, 1940-1943 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - United Steel Workers of America, Vincent D. Sweeney, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - USS Vincennes, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - University Catholic Club, 1944-1946 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Irish Room Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Minority Enrollment, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Urban America, Inc., 1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh, Welfare Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Urban Youth Action, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Utility Workers, 1942-1947 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Vietnam
    - Anti-War Activity at Carnegie-Mellon University, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Anti-War Protests, Pittsburgh, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Bucks County World Peace Fair, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Catholic Peace Fellowship, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Cleveland Convention, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, Following March to United Nations Building, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence in Regard to Debates with Justice Musmanno and Paul Long, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence in Response to Washington, D.C. Rally, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 32)